Henrik Lagrosen

helagro@outlook.com

PROFILE

I have extensive experience in IT support as an IT technician at Amplius Field Service Group AB and as a laboratory assistant at ALS Danderyd. Currently, I am studying Software Engineering and Management at the University of Gothenburg.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Technician, Amplius Field Service Group AB

As an IT technician, I was responsible for providing technical support and service to various clients. My role involved extensive fieldwork where I handled and resolved issues with variety of equipment, including Cisco devices, POS devices, and computers.

August 2022 — Present

Laboratory Assistant, ALS Danderyd

Responsible for preparing for and cleaning up after analysis. I also had additional responsibilities as key fob manager and IT support. The support involved installation and troubleshooting for computers, and connected devices.

April 2022 — August 2022, Danderyd

Shop Assistant, Ica Stillingsön

Cashier service and store maintenance.

June 2020 — July 2020, June 2019 — July 2019, Orust

EDUCATION

University of Gothenburg

Software Engineering and Management

2022 — Present, Gothenburg

Chalmers University of Technology

Information Technology

2021 — 2021, Gothenburg

Fria Läroverken

Technology, Information and Media

August 2019 — June 2021, Kalmar

Jensen Gymnasieskola

Technology, Information

August 2018 — June 2019, Gothenburg

QUALIFICATIONS

Programming

IT service

Web design

Android development

Fluent in English

Experience in image and

video editing

Proficient in Excel

TECHNIQUES

Android

 \mathbf{C}

C++

Flutter

HTML & CSS

Java

JavaScript

Kotlin

MongoDB

Postman

Python

SOL

Typescript

Vue





